

ALPER AKTAŞ

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT INFO

\ +90 534 621 81 05

contact@aktasalper.com

in /aktasalper/

aktasalper.com

Paca, İzmir / Turkey

EDUCATION

Ege University

English Language and Literature **2017 - 2022**

Küçükçekmece High School

Foreign Language Class

2015 - 2017

Çakmaklı Cumhuriyet High School 2013 - 2015

LANGUAGES

Turkish - Native

English - CEFR C1

REFERENCES

Çağrı Babuçcuoğlu

Software Lead, Front-end Team Lead

1Pixel Digital Agency

cagribabuccuoglu@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I am a 23 year old English Language and Literature graduate interested in software development. My entry to software development began with taking online courses on Python and building small projects with it, using various libraries. After I worked as a front-end developer intern, I have been primarily focusing on web development. I am currently working at Etstur as a software development assistant.

EXPERIENCES

JUL 25, 2022 - PRESENT

Etstur

OCT 2021 - NOV 2021

1Pixel Digital Agency

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT ASSISTANT

Front-end development for Etstur web applications.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER INTERN

Coding functional and responsive sections of pages that correspond to their respective graphical designs, which were provided as issues in Jira Agile development environment.

Integrating created page sections into Shopify themes to provide customizable and ease to use controls to merchants. In addition to integrating these sections to themes, fetching dynamic store data into page elements using Shopify Liquid templating language.

MAY 2020 - AUG 2021

Freelancer.com

FREELANCE VIDEO EDITOR

Editing & creating advertisement, music and presentation videos for clients

SKILLS & FAMILIARITY

FRONTEND

- > React
- > TypeScript
- > Vite / webpack
- > Next.js
- > Alpine.js

DBMS

- > MongoDB
- > PostgreSQL
- > SQLite

CERTIFICATES

React (Basic) HackerRank

10 Apr, 2022

Rest API (Intermediate)

HackerRank
11 Apr, 2022

Python Programming: From Beginner to Advanced

Bilgi Teknolojileri ve İletişim Kurumu

19 Aug, 2021

SQL (Basic) HackerRank

12 Aug, 2021